Translated by Releska
When I notice, all the dreams in that stage,
I always cry at the same time.
I just got a new head of the body,
so I'm happy to see it,
so I don't have to cry,
My shadow is not the same,
The picture of the door is so beautiful
You and you and you
If you love me with your hand
People will be closer to each other
How do you feel?
Are you feeling it?
If we were to test the machine, it would have been great.
We were so happy that we were able to work together.
I don't even know where to go.
But it's not the beginning.
It would be better to be friends with Mr. Kyo-ryu.
I'm happy to be here with Muka-muka.
Muka-muka and Yukidaru.
Is there a mountain in the mountain?
Yes, I found a place where the snowy forest is.
I have a place where I can find it.
I like it too.
It's so hot.
It's really hot.
It's the time when I went to the sea in the morning.
I remember.
The snowy forest became so cold.
Shut up!
I'm going to get you out of here!
I wanted to get you out of the way to the world of the West Valley!
Where are you going to get me out of here?
I'm not going to get you out of here, right?
Since they have not even been born yet.
I'm going to the sea!
I'm good at taking you out of the sea from the head!
The snowy forest and the snowy weather are all like this.
The weather has become so cold.
It feels like this is the best place in the world!
But it's not here.
It's impossible, isn't it?
Ah, that's not for food!
I made a rare one, so put it here.
It's a cake!
How's it? Is it good?
It's good, isn't it?
What's wrong with this?
There's a lot of stuff in the box.
It's a cake from the newspaper.
Put the blueberry milk in the box.
Oh, it's good!
It's good!
Oh, it's heavy!
Oh, it's heavy.
It's cold, isn't it?
When I eat it, my head hurts.
Got it?
It's heavy, isn't it?
It's heavy!
Yeah!
I can do it!
If you want to express it that way,
you can call your parents.
Okay!
I'm waiting for your call.
I'll call you later.
It's a cake!
I see.
I have to teach them how to eat it.
Huh?
Do you want to eat those people too?
Yeah.
Anyway, I'm a 5-year-old girl.
I understand.
I'm a 5-year-old girl.
Okay.
I'll teach you how to eat them.
I'm a 5-year-old girl.
Yes, I do.
It's not like that.
Don't say this.
Fine.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'm a 5-year-old girl.
He's a difficult person to use in a remote control system.
He doesn't know how to use a remote control system.
The controller is really fast.
He's very fast, too.
It's a fast and not very powerful.
It's easy to use in a remote control system.
Hey!
Oh!
Oh-oh!
Well, that was a good try.
Anyway, it was 3 minutes ago.
I was about to get it, so I didn't find it, but I will just keep it now.
5 minutes?
Is it going to be like a super speedy star?
Yes, I do.
Hey, give me the green onion.
Hey, I'm going to make you brown...
Hmm, I don't know if I can make it by one or two times in the morning!
I hope I can make it by one or two times in the morning.
Is it possible to make it by one or two times in the morning?
There's no way I can make it by one or two times in the morning!
If it gets worse, I can run away immediately.
It's good, it's good, it's good, it's good
I can find this blueberry
It's a good food
When you eat like this, you eat this
Sam-kun, where are you?
I'm starting, I'm Yuki Daruma
Yuki Daruma
Yes, thank you
Then, did you eat the blueberry soup?
Yes, I'm very hungry
I'm hungry
I'm sorry for making you hungry
Do you like to eat something like that?
I like to eat more than I do
However, there are many creatures in the world
I wonder if I can eat it
Do you live in Kurochikuku?
No, I live in Yukiyama
Have you been on the road with Sam-Polo?
No, actually, I...
I'm going to the sea
The sea?
Yes, it's the sea where the sun and the sun are shining
Is that the sea?
No, I'm not the one who saw the sea
So, I want to go to the sea
It's my dream
I'm going to the sea and go to the sea
I'll have to go to the sea
I'll go to the sea and go to the sea
I'm going to the sea and go to the sea
Yuki Daruma
But, you don't want to go to the sea?
I'm sure you're happy because there's a chance to talk
I see
We have a great time!
I see!
If you find the sea, we will teach you where we are!
I think it's easy!
Then I will do my best!
Good luck!
What are you doing?
Huh?
Are you going to sleep there?
I just went to Yuki-Daruma's place.
Don't you think you are going to sleep there?
Huh?
It's hard!
It's getting hot outside.
What kind of body is it?
It's getting hot.
Yuki-Daruma-kun!
Huh?
Are you okay?
No, I'm so tired.
It's not a hot day.
It's a body.
Hey, you idiot!
That's why you are going to Yuki-Daruma-kun.
Yuki-Daruma-kun is really weird!
You are going to return to Yuki-Daruma soon, right?
Yeah! Wait a minute!
Bye-bye!
See you later!
What should I do?
Hot.
Huh?
I see!
I can do it!
Where are you going?
Yeah!
I'm sorry.
I'm going to go to the hotel.
Have a little rest.
Well, if you go to Shibara-kun, you'll be fine.
Well, I'm going to Yuki-Daruma-kun.
If you are fine, you can't go to Yuki-Daruma-kun.
I'm going to return to Yuki-Daruma-kun.
What?
I'm not going to return to Yuki-Daruma-kun.
I'm going to return to Yuki-Daruma-kun.
If you go to Yuki-Daruma-kun, you'll be fine.
I don't want to get angry here.
Oh, I'm going to get angry here.
It will be fine.
I will be fine.
I'm actually going to return to Yuki-Daruma-kun.
W-wee!
Hey!
Thank you very much.
Are you going to stop the sea?
Yes.
Do you want to go to the sea with you?
What? Don't you know the sea?
Yes.
It's a good place to go.
Even if you look at it, you can feel it.
Even if you hear the waves, you can feel it.
If you look at the sea, you can feel it.
If you want to go, you can feel the weather's easing.
That's fun.
I think the sea will go far away.
What is the problem?
It is strange that you keep flying by the wind but never to fly.
What are you thinking?
It's exciting.
Where did you go to take care of the forest?
This is the first time I've ever been here.
Is Yukidaru able to take care of the forest after all?
If I take care of the forest, I'll take care of the forest.
I'll take care of the forest.
I have to look for Yukidaru to take care of the forest.
Yukidaru, wait for the forest of Akogare!
Please don't move because it's a bit too much.
Please.
Umm, a bit too long?
Oh, yeah.
It's because I came here and the forest is here.
You're going to take care of the forest of Akogare?
I am running away like this.
I was going to do a vire.
It's not a big deal, but a forest of Akogare?
Don't be afraid of your dad!
It's okay.
What is it?
Um...
I didn't see Yukidaru-maku?
Huh?
I-I'm not ready to go to the jungle collection, so I don't know what Yukidaru-maku is!
That's right.
Fight!
Yukidaru-maku can't go to Yukidaru-maku, so he can go to Yukidaru-maku.
That's why he came here.
Huh?
You'd like to go there and check Yukidaru-maku, right?
So, after that, you should go there.
Here you go.
Over there, right?
Really?
Where should I go?
The zombie's in the jungle.
She's Action that I like.
If I do that, I'll walk over here, and take out the tree!
Come on, come on, come on...
Over there.
Over there, over there, over there.
I can't go to the jungle.
Oh, no!
I'm so busy!
Ms. Doshuova!
What the hell?
Did you see Yukidai?
I don't have any idea what Yukidai is.
Oh, is there a sea next to this place?
If there's a sea, it will be 10 minutes.
Manzoku-dosu! Manzoku-dosu!
That's not true!
That's what we're talking about!
No way!
Are you all right?
No, no, no!
Where did you go?
Yukarama-kun, you're going away.
Huh?
Sentai!
Oh-chan!
I was surprised.
Yukidaro-kun is walking.
Are you looking at Yukidaro-kun?
Huh?
It was Muka-muka and Ishio-dasu.
Huh? Muka-muka-muka?
Yeah, it was Mori-no-muka.
Muka-muka-muka also made friends.
Ishigo?
Hey, what are you talking about?
Muka-muka-muka is Muka-muka!
Huh?
That's right.
Muka-muka and Ishio-dasu might be able to tell us about this pendant.
Huh?
Please, Yukidaro-kun, save Yukidaro-kun.
Muka-muka and Ishio-dasu might be able to tell us about this pendant.
Please, Yukidaro-kun!
What?
Here...
Where are you?
That mountain's ship?
Huh?
Ishigo?
Let's go now.
Thank you.
Well, well, don't worry about that.
You can't let your dreams come true.
You're so good at making your dreams.
It's so hot.
Muka-muka!
Muka-muka was tired.
If you look at me,
if you look at me,
I can feel it, right?
Muka-muka!
I wonder if I was able to do it.
I was able to do it until you came here.
But I can't let my dreams come true.
I can't let my dreams come true.
I was able to do it until you came here.
Muka-muka!
Muka-muka, are you okay?
It's so hot!
I don't have a day off.
What should I do?
Hey, baby!
I can't find it.
I'll bring you a fridge.
Hey!
No!
Thank you, Toku.
What? What?
I'll bring you a fridge.
Yay!
That's why it's so hot.
If you don't have a day off,
you can't let your dreams come true.
Muka-muka, are you okay?
It's a sea!
It's a sea.
Oh, it's still hot.
It's not hot.
It's a sea.
I love that.
I'm going to have a drink.
I love the drink.
Yay!
Wow!
Nice.
I'm great.
Hey, Toku.
Are you okay?
When you finally get here...
Hey...
Wait! Wait!
Nukaruka!
After the morning fresh, I prized enough herbs
Ay, ay, ay, ay, hey!
Baladas
Look at this, look at this, wait!
Look at this, no one is around
Take this name of mine
As I go, I dance.
I often come over and think that I'm at it.
I remember then,
and by the way,
what's changed?
The world we are,
I may not be able to tell.
If it's over, then it's a heart.
Bam, bam, bam, bam, bam.
I like it, I like it, I like it, I like it, I like it.
I hope I go to the end of every one of you.
It's so fun, you know,
it's a story, you know.
I haven't used up all the cards.
Why don't I use money?
I made a super hard deal,
but can't I even use a 6?
No way!
Mokamuka, what are you doing?
Maybe it's KING?
It's a real KING?
Next time, Mokamuka Paradise!
Mokamuka Sakinderu, Mokamuka!
I'm looking forward to...